{"computer" : {
    "question1": {
        "question":"Q1: What is the full form of CPU?",
        "a": ". Central Process Unit",
        "b": ". Central Processing Unit",
        "c": ". Central Programming Unit",
        "d": ". Central Progressive Unit",
        "correct": "b"
    },
    "question2": {
        "question": " Q2: What is the full form of ALU?",
        "a": ". Select all ",
        "b": ". Advance Logical Unit",
        "c": ". Arithmetic Local Unit",
        "d": ". Arithmetic Logic Unit",
        "correct": "d"
    },
    "question3": {
        "question": "Q3: What is an Internet?",
        "a": ". Interconnected computers from the world",
        "b": ". Select all",
        "c": ". Wide Area Network",
        "d": ". Network of Network",
        "correct": "b"
    },
    "question4": {
        "question": "Q4: What does an Operating System do?",
        "a": ". Memory Management",
        "b": ". File Management",
        "c": ". Application Management",
        "d": ". All of the above",
        "correct": "d"
    },
    "question5": {
        "question": "Q5: Which part of the computer is considered as Brain of the Computer?",
        "a": ". Read Only Memory",
        "b": ". Random Access Memory",
        "c": ". Central Process Unit",
        "d": ". Hard Disk",
        "correct": "c"
    }

},

"css":
    {
        "question1": {
            "question":"Q1:  If We Want Define Style For An Unique Element, Then Which Css Selector Will We Use ?",
            "a": ". Text ",
            "b": ". ID",
            "c": ". Class",
            "d": ". Name ",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        "question2": {
            "question": " Q2:  Which CSS Property Sets The Stack Order Of An Element?",
            "a": ". Overflow",
            "b": ". Position",
            "c": ". Clip",
            "d": ". Z-index",
            "correct": "d"
        },
        "question3": {
            "question": "Q3: Which Of The Following Selector Selects An Element That Has No Children?",
            "a": ". No-child",
            "b": ". Empty",
            "c": ". Inheritance",
            "d": ". Select all",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        "question4": {
            "question": "Q4: How Can We Write Comment Along With CSS Code ?",
            "a": ". / A Comment /",
            "b": ". <' A Comment'>",
            "c": ". // A Comment //",
            "d": ". /* A Comment */",
            "correct": "d"
        },
        "question5": {
            "question": "Q5:  Which CSS Property Sets A Background Image For An Element?",
            "a": ". Background - Attachment",
            "b": ". Background - Color",
            "c": ". Background - Image",
            "d": ". None of These",
            "correct": "c"
        }
    
    },

"english":
{
    "question1": {
        "question":"Q1: A:_____ did you live in New York? B:I lived there for almost five years.",
        "a": ". When",
        "b": ". How long",
        "c": ". How much",
        "d": ". Nothing",
        "correct": "b"
    },
    "question2": {
        "question": " Q2: They threw a rock _____ the window and broke the glass.",
        "a": ". across",
        "b": ". into",
        "c": ". nothing",
        "d": ". through",
        "correct": "d"
    },
    "question3": {
        "question": "Q3: He didn't speak English, _____ it was difficult to make him understand what he had to do.",
        "a": ". although",
        "b": ". so",
        "c": ". a+b",
        "d": ". because",
        "correct": "b"
    },
    "question4": {
        "question": "Q4: Why did you turn off the TV? B: Because I _____. I'm very tired.",
        "a": ". go to sleep",
        "b": ". will go to sleep",
        "c": ". select all",
        "d": ". 'm going to sleep",
        "correct": "d"
    },
    "question5": {
        "question": "Q5: This is the famous wine _____ is produced in this region.",
        "a": ". where",
        "b": ". that it",
        "c": ". which",
        "d": ". when",
        "correct": "c"
    }

}

}